pointstreak.com 2009-06-16

# Pointstreak.com - privacy policy - The Leader in Sports Management Solutions

Pointstreak.com Inc. strongly believes in keeping the trust of our leagues, players, partners and employees. We believe that by protecting the personal information of our customers and maintaining a high level of integrity, we will help accelerate the rate at which people are comfortable with using our innovative service. This privacy policy is designed to inform you, the user, about what information Pointstreak gathers about you, how this information is used and how it is protected.

Your Personal Information

* * *

Through the operation of Pointstreak's service, Pointstreak or the league administrator may request or require personal information, such as your name, email address(es), phone number(s), address and other demographic information. It is the purpose of this policy to inform you of how this information is used and protected. Any personal information that is collected is either used for the operation of our service, that is, to collect and display hockey statistics, or by the league administrator, in the normal operation of their league. We may use aggregate data to develop a profile of the general population of our users for use in business development and communication with partners or clients. However, in no way will Pointstreak use or share your personal, individual information with any third party.

Website Usage 

* * *

Pointstreak uses standard log files to analyze website traffic. Any information we collect is used for internal purposes to improve the content, features or overall service of the website; to enhance users' experiences when visiting Pointstreak's website; to customize the content, design or layout of our pages; and to provide the services required by an individual user or league. We do not use personal information for any reason that is not disclosed either in this privacy policy or at the time the information is requested.

Third Party Disclosure

* * *

Pointstreak does not share your personal information with any third party without your permission. We disclose, only in aggregate form, our statistical analyses or demographics of users to third parties, such as sponsors or business partners. This aggregate information does not include names, email addresses or any other individual-specific or identifying information. 

User Information Accuracy

* * *

Questions regarding Pointstreak's privacy policy or the use of the information collected should be directed via email to [info@pointstreak.com](mailto:info@pointstreak.com), by telephone at (604) 734-3585, or by mail to: 

Pointstreak.com Inc.  
1627 West Broadway, Suite #202  
Vancouver, BC  
V6J 1W9

Questions regarding the accuracy of your personal information or hockey statistics should be taken up with your league or database administrator - NOT Pointstreak staff or management.

Security of Information 

* * *

Pointstreak has taken all necessary measures to ensure that our customer's and user's information is as secure as possible. A league administrator has password-protected access to his/her database through secured Internet encryption technologies. When we collect information from our customers or users, it is stored in an area to which the general public does not have access.

Opting-out 

* * *

Whenever appropriate, website users will be given the choice to "opt-out" of any uses of their personal information, such as email bulletins. Aside from an automatic reply to an email received by us, it is our intent not to email to you unless you request a particular service, or consent to being contacted by email. There may be instances where you will have the opportunity to subscribe to an email list that will send you the appropriate information, but this will be continued only with your permission and consent throughout the duration of the service. You, the user, may opt-out, at any time, of any service that you have signed up for in the past through Pointstreak's service and website.

Effect of Privacy Policy

* * *

This privacy policy is effective and up-to-date as of November 1st, 2001. Pointstreak reserves the right to change this policy at any time and will post any changes to this policy as soon as they go into effect.  

* * *
